Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art registrar's office records, 1869-2013 COR0005.1.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Exhibition files, 1980-2014; Series 9
  - Views and Visions - lenders: Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1986-1988; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: Mr. Leonard Milberg, 1986-1987; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: Mrs. Edward P. Moore, 1986-1987; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: Museum of Fine Arts, Boston, 1984-1986; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: Museum of Fine Arts, Houston, 1984-1986; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: Museum of Early Southern Decorative Arts, 1982-1987; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: Moratorium at the national Gallery of Canada, 1985-1986; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: National Museum of American History, 1986; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: New Britain Museum of American Art, 1984-1986; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: New Jersey Historical Society, 1985-1986; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: New Jersey State museum, 1985-1986; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: The New York Historical Society, 1985-1987; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: New York Public library, 1986-1987; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: Old Sturbridge Village, 1985-1987; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: Mrs. John M. Patterson, 1986-1987; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: Pennsylvania Academy of Fine Arts, 1984-1987; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: Pennsylvania Hospital, 1985-1987; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: The Charles Rand Penny Collection, 1985-1986; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: Philadelphia Print Shop, 1984-1986; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: Portland Museum of Art, 1985-1986; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: Public Archives of Canada (Ottawa), 1985-1987; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: Reynolds House Museum of American Art, 1986-1987; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: Rhode Island School of Design Thomas Cole: Landscape with tree trunks, 1987 April 25-June 21; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: Ricau Collection (Mark Umbach), 1986; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Views and Visions - [lenders: Royal Ontario Museum], 1985-1986; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: Shelburne Museum, 1985-1986; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: Society for the Preservation of New England Antiquities, 1985-1986; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: Victor D. Spark, 1984-1986; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: United States Department of State Diplomatic Reception Room, 1986-1987; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: Terra Museum of American Art, 1984-1987; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: Toledo Museum of Art, 1984-1986; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: Virginia State Library, 1986; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: Pennsylvania State University Dr. Vessell, 1985-1986; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: Wadsworth Atheneum, 1985-1986; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 37)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: Gulf States Paper Corp. (Warner collection), 1986-1987; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 38)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: Mr. and Mrs. Frank Wilkins, 1985-1987; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 39)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: Winterthur Museum and Gardens, 1985-1987; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 40)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: Worcester Art Museum, 1984-1987; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 41)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: Yale Center for British Art, 1986-1987; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 42)
  - Views and Visions - lenders: Yale University Art Gallery, 1985-1987; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 43)
  - Color Photographs from the Farm Security administation - Installation plans, 1987; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 44)
  - Color Photographs from the Farm Security administation, 1983-1987; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 45)
  - Women Artists from the Corcoran gallery of art; drawings, 1987; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 46)
  - 40th Biennial - Insurance lists and certificates copies, 1986-1987; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 47)
  - 40th Biennial - Dispersal, 1987; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 48)
  - 40th Biennial - Lists (checklist, shipping), 1987; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 49)
  - 40th Biennial - shipping (vendors and lists), 1987; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 50)
  - 40th Biennial - condition notes and receipts, 1987; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 51)
  - 40th Biennial - Installation plans and photos, 1987; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 52)
  - 40th Corcoran - Biennial memos, 1986 April 11-June 21; Series 9 (Box 47, Folder 53)
  - Black Folk Art in America - Condition notes: 1-20, 1982; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Black Folk Art in America - Condition notes: 21-40, 1982; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Black Folk Art in America - Condition notes: 41-60, 1982; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Black Folk Art in America - Condition notes: 61-80, 1982; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Black Folk Art in America - Condition notes: 81-100, 1982; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Black Folk Art in America - Condition notes: 101-120, 1982; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Black Folk Art in America - Condition notes: 121-140, 1982; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Black Folk Art in America - Condition notes: 141-160, 1982; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Black Folk Art in America - Condition notes: 161-180, 1982; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Black Folk Art in America - Condition notes: 181-200, 1982; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Black Folk Art in America - Condition notes: 201-220, 1982; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Black Folk Art in America - Condition notes: 221-240, 1982; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Black Folk Art in America - Condition notes: 241-260, 1982; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Black Folk Art in America - Condition notes: 261-280, 1982; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Black Folk Art in America - Condition notes: 281-300, 1982; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Black Folk Art in America - Condition notes: 300-320, 1982; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Black Folk Art in America - Condition notes: 321-340, 1982; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Black Folk Art in America - Condition notes: 341-360, 1982; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Black Folk Art in America - Condition notes: 361-380, 1982; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Black Folk Art in America - Condition notes: 381-391, 1982; Series 9 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - An Uncertain Grace: Photography by Sebastiao Salgado, 1992 January 11-February 22; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Songs of My People: African-Americans, A Self-Portrait, 1992 February 15-May 3; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - GALLERY ONE: Maurizio Pellegrin, 1992 March 7-April 19; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - GALLERY ONE: Guillermo Kuitca, 1992 May 9-July 19; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Interface: Berlin Art in the Nineties, 1992 May 23-July 5; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Max Weber: The Cubist Decade, 1910-1920, 1992; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Kieth Haring, Andy Warhol, and Walt Disney, 1992 June 6-August 16; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - From Sea to Shining Sea: A Portrait of America, Photographs by Hiroji Kubota, 1992 July 4-September 13; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - A Brush With Disney: The Art of Herbert Dickens Ryman - Shipping and Installation, 1992 July 16-September 6; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - A Brush With Disney: The Art of Herbert Dickens Ryman - Loan Agreements and Condition, 1992 July 16-September 6; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Fata Morgana USA: The American Way of Life, 1992 September 5-November 8; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Covert Obsolescence: Installations by Jim Sanborn, 1992 September 12-November 8; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Washington By Night: Vintage Photographs from the 1930s by Volkmar Kurt Wentzel, 1992 September 12-1993 January 3; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Cavaliers and Cardinals: Nineteenth Century French Anecdotal Painting, 1992 September 19-November 8; Series 9 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - 42nd Biennial - Photos, 1991 September 7 - November 10; Series 9 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - GALLERY ONE: William T. Wiley - Condition Reports, 1991 May 11-July; Series 9 (Box 51, Folders 2-3)
  - GALLERY ONE: William T. Wiley, 1991 May 11-July; Series 9 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Robert Rauschenberg: The Early 1950s, 1991 June 15-August 11; Series 9 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Berenice Abbott, Photographer: A Modern Vision, 1991 July 20-September 29; Series 9 (Box 51, Folders 6-7)
  - 42nd Biennial Exhibition of Contemporary American Painting, 1991 September 7-November 10; Series 9 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - 42nd Biennial Exhibition of Contemporary American Painting - Installation Photographs, 1991 September 7-November 10; Series 9 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - 42nd Biennial Exhibition of Contemporary American Painting - Purchase Orders, 1991 September 7-November 10; Series 9 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - 42nd Biennial Exhibition of Contemporary American Painting - Loan Agreements A-D, 1991 September 7-November 10; Series 9 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - 42nd Biennial Exhibition of Contemporary American Painting - Loan Agreements E-K, 1991 September 7-November 10; Series 9 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - 42nd Biennial Exhibition of Contemporary American Painting - Loan Agreements L-P, 1991 September 7-November 10; Series 9 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - 42nd Biennial Exhibition of Contemporary American Painting - Loan Agreements Q-Z, 1991 September 7-November 10; Series 9 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - 42nd Biennial Exhibition of Contemporary American Painting - Checklist/Insurance List, 1991 September 7-November 10; Series 9 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - 42nd Biennial Exhibition of Contemporary American Painting - Shipping List, 1991 September 7-November 10; Series 9 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - 42nd Biennial Exhibition of Contemporary American Painting - Condition Reports, 1991 September 7-November 10; Series 9 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Joyce Scott: I-con-no-body/I-con-o-graphy, 1991 September 14-November 17; Series 9 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Sport in Art from American Museums, 1991 September 21-December 8; Series 9 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Alfred Hutty and the Charleston Renaissance, 1991 October 12-December 15; Series 9 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Lou Stovall: Heroes, Teachers, and Friends, 1991 October 12-December 15; Series 9 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Typologies: Nine Contemporary Photographers, 1991 November 23-January 19; Series 9 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - The Body Electric: Zizi Raymond and Kiki Smith, 1991 December 14-1992 February 16; Series 9 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Worthington Whittredge: Hudson River Artist, 1990 September 8-November 4; Series 9 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Haden, Whistler, Pennell: Three Master Printmakers in the Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1990 September 8-December 9; Series 9 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - James Drake: Place and Passage, 1990 September 15-November 11; Series 9 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Inability to Endure or Deny the World: Representation and Text in the Work of Robert Morris, 1990 December 8-1991 February 19; Series 9 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Inability to Endure or Deny the World: Representation and Text in the Work of Robert Morris, 1990 December 8-1991 February 17; Series 9 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Transgressions: Donald Lipski and Buzz Spector, 1990 December 8-1991 February 10; Series 9 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - William Eggleston: The Democratic Forest, 1990 December 15-1991 February 24; Series 9 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Tony Cragg: Sculpture, 1991 February 2-March 31; Series 9 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Thomas Kovachevich: Seeing Invisible Things, 1991 March 2-April 14; Series 9 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - George de Vincent: Journey in Time, A 40th Anniversary Celebration of Arena Stage, 1991 March 9-April 21; Series 9 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Reckoning with Winslow Homer: His Late Works and Their Influence, 1991 March 16-May 12; Series 9 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Changing Reality: Recent Soviet Photography, 1991 May 11-July 17; Series 9 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - GALLERY ONE: William T. Wiley - General Information, 1991 May 11-July 28; Series 9 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - GALLERY ONE: William T. Wiley - Loan Agreements and Lender Info, 1991 May 11-July 28; Series 9 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - GALLERY ONE: William T. Wiley - Shipping and Crating, 1991 May 11-July 28; Series 9 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Thirty-Seventh Biennial Exhibition of Contemporary American Painting, 1981; Series 9 (Box 53, Folders 1-3)
  - P.H. Polk Photography Exhibition, 1981 March 21-May 17; Series 9 (Box 53, Folders 4-5)
  - The American West: Selections from the Anschutz Collection and the Corcoran Collection, 1981 March 25-April 26; Series 9 (Box 53, Folders 6-9)
  - Archives exhibition: Portrait of a Dream, 1981 March 27-June 30; Series 9 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - The Artist as Illustrator, 1981 March 31-June 14; Series 9 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Henri Cartier-Bresson, 1981 April 4-May 17; Series 9 (Box 53, Folders 12-13)
  - Adolph Gottlieb: A Retrospective, 1981 April 15-June 6; Series 9 (Box 53, Folders 14-15)
  - Student Show, 1981 April 28-May 10; Series 9 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - The Washington Series: Collage on Paper - Catalogue, 1981; Series 9 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - The Washington Series: Collage on Paper, 1981; Series 9 (Box 53, Folders 18-19)
  - Peter Thomas: Corcoran After Hours, 1981 May 13-June 28; Series 9 (Box 53, Folders 20-23)
  - The Red Cross in Black and White, 1981 May 17-July 5; Series 9 (Box 53, Folders 24-25)
  - Frederick Sommer at Seventy-Five, 1981 May 22-July 5; Series 9 (Box 53, Folders 26-27)
  - Frank Wright: Paintings, 1981 June 13-July 19; Series 9 (Box 53, Folders 28-31)
  - Photographers X Photographers, 1981 June 18-July 26; Series 9 (Box 53, Folders 32-33)
  - Early America on Paper: Prints and Drawings 1750-1850, 1981; Series 9 (Box 53, Folders 34-35)
  - 37th Biennial - Installation slides, 1981; Series 9 (Box 53, Folder 36)
  - The Art of Archibald J. Motley, Jr., 1992 October 10-1993 January 3; Series 9 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Reverberations, 1992 December 5-1992 January 31; Series 9 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Africa Explores: 20th Century African Art, 1993 February 13-April 4; Series 9 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Antony Gormley, 1993 February 13-April 11; Series 9 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Karsh: American Legends, 1993 February 27-April 18; Series 9 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Marinus Boezem, 1993 June 5-August 1; Series 9 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Rescuers of the Holocaust: Portraits by Gay Block, 1993 June 16-September 6; Series 9 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - The Century Association Collection, 1993 July 21-September 13; Series 9 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Visiones del Pueblo: Latin American Folk Art, 1993 August 14-October 10; Series 9 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - I Remember... Thirty Years After the March on Washington: Images of the Civil Rights Movement 1963-1993, 1993 August 28-October 10; Series 9 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Fables and Fantasies: The Art of Felix Lorioux, 1993 June 6-August 22; Series 9 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Asafo! African Flags of the Fante, 1993 September 11-November 15; Series 9 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - 43rd Biennial Exhibition of Contemporary American Painting - Condition Reports, 1993 October 30-1994 January 2; Series 9 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - 43rd Biennial Exhibition of Contemporary American Painting - Insurance, 1993 October 30-1994 January 2; Series 9 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - 43rd Biennial Exhibition of Contemporary American Painting - Checklist, 1993 October 30-1994 January 2; Series 9 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Jacob Kainen: Seven Paintings and Three Drawings, 1993 September 11-1994 January 2; Series 9 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - 43rd Biennial Exhibition of Contemporary American Painting - Anderson-Edward Thorpe Gallery, 1993 October 30-1994 January 2; Series 9 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - 43rd Biennial Exhibition of Contemporary American Painting - L.A. Louver-Rabb, 1993 October 30-1994 January 2; Series 9 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - 43rd Biennial Exhibition of Contemporary American Painting - Fred Hoffman-Koplin Gallery, 1993 October 30-1994 January 2; Series 9 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - 43rd Biennial Exhibition of Contemporary American Painting - Ronald Feldman-Westendarp, 1993 October 30-1994 January 2; Series 9 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - 43rd Biennial Exhibition of Contemporary American Painting - Artists/Dealers/Collectors Lists, 1993 October 30-1994 January 2; Series 9 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - 43rd Biennial Exhibition of Contemporary American Painting - Return Shipping Arrangements, 1993 October 30-1994 January 2; Series 9 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - 43rd Biennial Exhibition of Contemporary American Painting - Receipts, 1993 October 30-1994 January 2; Series 9 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - 43rd Biennial Exhibition of Contemporary American Painting - Incoming Shipping Arrangements, 1993 October 30-1994 January 2; Series 9 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Dorothy Dehner: 60 Years of Her Art, 1993 December 18-1994 March 7; Series 9 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - History Painting in America, 1775-1925, 1994 January 29-April 2; Series 9 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Meeting History: Treasures From Washington Region Private Collections, Historic Houses, and the Public Trust, 1994 January 29-April 10; Series 9 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - The Return of the Cadavre Exquis, 1994 February 5-April 10; Series 9 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Danny Lyon; Photo Film, 1994 February 5-April 3; Series 9 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Farewell to Bosnia: New Photographs by Gilles Peress, 1994 March 5-May 2; Series 9 (Box 56, Folders 19-20)
  - Farewell to Bosnia: New Photographs by Gilles Peress - Condition Reports 1, 1994 March 5-May 2; Series 9 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Farewell to Bosnia: New Photographs by Gilles Peress - Condition Reports 2, 1994 March 5-May 2; Series 9 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - The Scholastic Art Awards National Exhibition of 1994, 1994 May 21-June 27; Series 9 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Art Sites 6, 1994 May 25-July 3; Series 9 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Still Working - Receipts, etc., 1994 June 18-August 21; Series 9 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Still Working, 1994 June 18-August 21; Series 9 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - GALLERY ONE: Luxor v1.0 - An Interactive Installation by Y. David Chung, Matt Dibble, and Renee Stout, 1994 September 17-November 7; Series 9 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Louise Bourgeois: The Locust of Memory, 1994 September 24-1995 January 8; Series 9 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - The World of Lois Mailou Jones, 1994 September 17-November 14; Series 9 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Vaclav Havel: A Word About Words, 1994 November 30-1995 February 20; Series 9 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Larry Sultan: Pictures From Home, 1994 December 3-1995 February 6; Series 9 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Gallery One: Family Lives, 1994 December 10-1995 February 13; Series 9 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Off the Mall II (Hemicycle), 1994 November 19-December 26; Series 9 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Countdown to Eternity, Photographs of Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. in the 1960s by Ben Fernandez, 1995 January 14-February 20; Series 9 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Alphonse Legros, 1994 January 25-1995 May 1; Series 9 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Recent Acquisitions, 1995 February 25-April 10; Series 9 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Passionate Visions of the American South: Self-Taught Artists from 1940 to the Present, 1995 March 4-May 7; Series 9 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Pedro Mayer: Truth and Fictions, A Journey from Documentary to Digital Photography, 1995 March 11-May 15; Series 9 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Avant-Garde Photography: 1910-1945, 1995 May 3-August 7; Series 9 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Alfred Stieglitz's Camera Notes, 1995 May 6-July 9; Series 9 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Gallery One: Pervasiveness of Memory, 1995 May 20-September 10; Series 9 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Scholastic Art Awards National Exhibition, 1995 May 27-July 4; Series 9 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Color and Abstraction - Washington (1955-1975), 1995 June 3-August 20; Series 9 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - American Politicians: Photographs, 1995 July 14-September 4; Series 9 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Discovering Ellis Ruley, 1995 September 2 - October 29; Series 9 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Raised by Wolves: Photographs and Documents of Runaways by Jim Goldberg - Lenders and General, 1995 September 16-November 19; Series 9 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Raised by Wolves: Photographs and Documents of Runaways by Jim Goldberg - Installation Notebook, 1995 September 16-November 19; Series 9 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Raised by Wolves: Photographs and Documents of Runaways by Jim Goldberg - Venues, 1995 September 16-November 19; Series 9 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Raised by Wolves: Photographs and Documents of Runaways by Jim Goldberg - Condition Reports #1-33, 1995 September 16-November 19; Series 9 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Raised by Wolves: Photographs and Documents of Runaways by Jim Goldberg - Condition Reports #34-59, 1995 September 16-November 19; Series 9 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Raised by Wolves: Photographs and Documents of Runaways by Jim Goldberg - Condition Reports #60-90, 1995 September 16-November 19; Series 9 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Raised by Wolves: Photographs and Documents of Runaways by Jim Goldberg - Condition Reports #91-120, 1995 September 16-November 19; Series 9 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Raised by Wolves: Photographs and Documents of Runaways by Jim Goldberg - Condition Reports #121-150, 1995 September 16-November 19; Series 9 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Raised by Wolves: Photographs and Documents of Runaways by Jim Goldberg - Condition Reports #151-Text Panel #11, 1995 September 16-November 19; Series 9 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Raised by Wolves: Photographs and Documents of Runaways by Jim Goldberg - Crating, Transport and Invoices, 1995 September 16-November 19; Series 9 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Gallery One: Sculpture by Niek Kemp - Shipping Documents, 1995 September 23-December 3; Series 9 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Gallery One: Sculpture by Niek Kemp - Shipping Sea Freight Containers/Photos, etc., 1995 September 23-December 3; Series 9 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Raised by Wolves: Photographs and Documents of Runaways by Jim Goldberg - Dispersal, 1995; Series 9 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Gallery One: Sculpture by Niek Kemp - Insurance, 1995; Series 9 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Gallery One: Sculpture by Niek Kemp - Lists, Installation Correspondence, 1995; Series 9 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Gallery One: Sculpture by Niek Kemp - Purchase Orders, 1995; Series 9 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Gallery One: Sculpture by Niek Kemp - Lenders, Loan Agreements; Receipts; Condition Reports; Correspondence, 1995; Series 9 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Richard Bolton - Souvenir: Chronique d'Abidjan, 1995 December 6-1996 January 14; Series 9 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Maurice Prendergast, American Painter and Printmaker, 1995 December 16-1996 March 11; Series 9 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - In the Spirit of the Land: Recent Works by William Dunlap, 1995 December 6-1996 January 29; Series 9 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - 44th Biennial Exhibition of Contemporary Painting - Lenders, 1995 December 16-1996 February 19; Series 9 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - 44th Biennial Exhibition of Contemporary Painting - Condition Reports, 1995 December 16-1996 February 19; Series 9 (Box 59, Folder 5)